fancydresscostumes.co.uk 2016-06-22

# Privacy Policy - FancyDressCostumes.co.uk

**Privacy Policy**

At FancyDressCostumes.co.uk we consider your online safety to be of paramount importance. We also make every effort to ensure that your privacy is preserved when visiting this website. This Privacy Policy provides an explanation as to what happens to the personal data that you supply to us. Please be advised we do update this Policy from time to time, so please review this document regularly to keep sufficiently updated.

**Information we collect**

A.    Details of your visits to this website and the resources within this website that you access, including but not limited to, traffic data, location data, weblogs, and other relevant communication data.

B.    Information that you have voluntary provided by completing forms on this website, such as when you register for an account or make a transaction.

C.    Information provided to us when you communicate with us for any reason, including but not limited to, emails, telephone, & facsimile.

D.    Use of Cookies.

E.    We gather basic information about your computer or mobile device, such as the operating system or internet browser you are using, which enables us to optimise and improve general customer experience of this website.   

F.    Such information will not identify you personally, it will be aggregated into statistical data that will be used on a daily basis to analyse general visitor behavior. This statistical data does not identify any personal details whatsoever.

On occasion we gather details about your general online activity through cookie files. These cookie files are downloaded to your computer automatically and are stored on your hard drive. This is very much standard practice across the internet, as it assists us as a retailer in improving the level of service that we are able to provide to you. If this is not to your liking please note that all computers have a built in tool that enables them to decline the use of cookies. To do this, you will need to access the “Tool” menu in your internet browser. Please be advised that if cookies are not used, you may be unable to access particular parts of this website.

**Use of your information**

All of the information that we gather relating to you as a person is primarily used to optimise the quality of service that we are able to provide to you as the customer. In addition to this, we will occasionally use information for the following purposes:

A.    To provide you with information and promotions relating to our products.

B.    To contact you via email, post, or telephone, about any changes to this website that may affect the service that we are able to provide to you.

**Storing your personal data**

We have the ability to transfer data that we collect from you to locations outside of the European Economic Area for processing and storing. This may include but is not limited to internal databases, company staff, suppliers, and data management services. By submitting your personal data through this website, you agree to this transfer, storing or processing. All reasonable safety measures are executed to ensure that your data is treated in a safe and secure fashion.

Details relating to all transactions entered into this website will be encrypted to ensure a maximum level of reasonable safety is being reached. Please note that transmission of information via the internet is never completely secure, no matter how it is performed, which means that we cannot 100% guarantee the complete security of data sent to our system electronically. All transmission of such data is therefore completely at your own risk.

If you have registered for an account, you are completely responsible for keeping the associated password with this account confidential. We recommend for security purposes that on no occasion should you disclose your password to a third party. We will also never contact you via email, telephone, or facsimile requesting your password. We reserve the right to disclose your personal information to third parties, such as government departments, where we are legally required to disclose such information.

**Third party links**

This website may contain links to third party websites from time to time. These third party websites should have their own privacy policies, which you should check before using. We cannot and will not accept any responsibility or liability for their policies, as we have no control over them.  

**Contacting us**

We would love to hear from you if you have any questions regarding this privacy policy. If so, please drop an email here: [contact@fancydresscostumes.co.uk](mailto:contact@fancydresscostumes.co.uk)

**Access to information**

The 1998 Data Protection Act gives you the right to access the information that we currently store about you. Please note that by doing this you will be subject to a paying small processing fee of £10.

Should you wish to receive these details please write to the below address with the subject heading “1998 Data Protection Act Request” and include your contact details such as telephone number, email, & address. We will then respond within 10 working days to verify your identity and request payment of the £10 processing fee.

FancyDressCostumes.co.uk

The Old Vicarage

Lower Road

East Farleigh

Maidstone

Kent

ME15 0JW
